so how do you know if the business that
you're going to put out there is
marketable or that people are going to
buy it when you launch it you don't want
to waste time but sometimes we don't
always know if things are going to work
out by the end of this video I'm going
to be giving you my secret strategy for
knowing if a business is profitable if
it's worth your time doing as well as a
few really fun exercises that you can
walk through that will help you do this
now for those of you that I haven't met
yet my name is Jeremiah Kowski and for
the last 21 years I built multiple
businesses in the online info publishing
online coaching digital course space
back then they weren't called courses
they were DVDs and CD products that we
sold and then we did seminars in person
or Tela seminars what you see here today
we did the same stuff 21 years ago we're
making tens of millions of dollars but
now it's all come on digital and it's
way better digital to be honest with you
and so what I do now is I help people
that are getting started make their
first 5 10 15
$25,000 per month and I I'm really
believe in consistency I Believe In You
creating consistent Revenue the best way
that I know how to do that is with a
group mentoring coaching program that
combines courses with some kind of
coaching in a membership subscription
based model when you can kind of bring
all of those pieces together man it's a
recipe for success you can have a down
month where you have no sales and yet
you can still make 2030 $40,000 a month
that's the life that I live that's the
life that that my clients have lived for
years and that's what I love setting
people up doing and here's the truth
just selling a digital course by itself
these
days gosh I I've seen the statistics
course sales are down by themselves okay
so people are wanting more they're
wanting Community they're wanting con
connection they're wanting deeper they
want more specific as well and so how do
you know so that you don't waste your
time what is specific what are people
actually wanting and how to connect with
that well I'm going to give you those
strategies here today and how to
actually create offers that attract
people to you so that you don't have to
wonder is this going to work there's a
way to produce
predictable profits in your business how
many y'all like consistency and PR
predictability and what you can rely on
and what you can count on first off some
of y'all might be wondering what's this
funky thing on my nose here we have a
little bit of a nasal thing going around
here uh and so it's it's harder for me
to breathe and to get uh air up to my
brain and so I was like okay I'm going
to put this on fixed everything and so
I'm going like I know it looks a little
bit silly I'm going to leave it on it
helps a lot something that I Ed all
right so let's go dive right into it how
do you know that things are marketable
for you that they're actually going to
work I'm going to tell you something
that maybe you don't want to hear um and
you probably already know what I'm going
to say when I say that is is in reality
in business and this is something that
you have to realize there's no
guarantees there's no certainty even
when you have the track record that I do
of success things change the market
changes where things go what things are
doing and all of that changes and it
shifts and it's not going to remain the
same forever and now we have a world
that is different than we've ever
experienced to where algorithms
artificial intelligence all of those
things come together and while they're
amazing what's happening is is that
people's um resistance to marketing I
call this um marketing resistance kind
of like drug resistance is what it is
like if you think of if you take too
much of a drug and you're getting an
illness the body becomes resistant to
that marketing becomes the same way
people start to recognize oh that's just
marketing oh this is just them trying to
sell me something and so you might be
saying well Jeremiah I don't want to
just sell people stuff I don't want to
just Market stuff to people and totally
I get it you want to have an impact you
want to create something that you can
leave a legacy with you can create the
kind of income that you want to have can
I tell you this though you're not going
to have that unless you Market something
unless you have something that you can
put out there into the marketplace to
sell to people that they are going to
buy from you and so when we talk about
you generating an an income let's say
you just want to bring in an extra
$5,000 this month well you have to find
a way to get
$5,000 from people who have it okay and
so they're going to give you that $5,000
now in exchange for
this what you should be giving them at
least in some capacity or another is at
least
25,000 to
$50,000 in value in perceived value okay
and now this you might be like well wait
a sec I don't know if I have anything
that's $25 to $50,000 in perceived value
okay let's break this down very very
simply for you okay and I'm going to
show you how simple this is once you
understand this concept let's say that
you sell a product for
$100 okay and you get 50 people to buy
that
product okay 50 people to buy it that's
$5,000 right there and so the way that
you offer $225,000 of value is you
divide that by the 50 people so really
what it is is there're spending $100
with you but you're giving them about
$500 of value right there and this is
where I truly believe that your belief
in yourself your self-worth how you see
yourself how you perceive yourself and
getting rid of the comparison of feeling
like oh I'm not as good as those other
people out there or I'm not as good as
that or I can't do things as good as
they are can I tell you this the brain
is a
beautiful wonderful
creation that has become very very good
at one
thing keeping you alive
survival so that you don't
die for lack of a better word
right and so the the the the the human
mind because we're all humans that are
watching this unless an AI is reading my
text well then you're not a human
but actually I'm not kidding every AI is
actually reading all of the different
videos on YouTube right now and and and
and that's one of the reasons why I'm
creating a lot of these different video
pieces of content is cuz I know that
that's a whole other topic IC for
another time
okay your brain is very very good at
keeping you alive and survival and it
focuses on survival Instinct based
information
okay what is survival Instinct based
information that means that it's always
going to gravitate towards what's not
working
what you don't have right
now what you are unable to do right now
what you are trying to avoid happening I
don't want to launch something that's
not marketable I don't want to waste
time selling something that's going to
be a waste of my time I don't want to
invest money that I'm not don't get a
guaranteed return on okay and again I
understand
this can I tell you this is that there
is no guarantees when it comes to
business there is no guarantees when it
comes to putting yourself out there and
some of you may not want to hear that
and you're looking for somebody on
YouTube to tell you that there's a
guarantee you want to know what sets me
apart and why my clients get so many
results we've helped thousands of people
create businesses in the info publishing
space online courses digital products
coaching mentoring seminars webinars
because I tell people the truth that
nobody else is going to tell
them and that doesn't actually make me
very popular in fact it actually makes
it to where there are people that I
probably could sell stuff to them if I
was
dishonest okay but I can't do that I
couldn't sleep at night if I wasn't
actually telling you the truth and so I
have to tell you that while it is not
easy it is simple to be able to do this
and I want you to start to believe that
for yourself it may not be easy there
will be hard things you will have to do
stuff that challenges you every single
day and can I encourage you in this you
got to start doing the hard stuff more
often you got to start doing the stuff
that inside of you feels
impossible now you might not do it
overnight and it might take you some
time and you may need to have a Mentor
help you you may need to join a
community of people like what we have
going on over and in my client growth
accelerator program you can find it over
at my website at Jeremiah kurowski dcom
under coaching group coaching program
it's not enrollment is not open right
now but there is a waiting list and what
we do is it is an immersive Community
where we work with you where we come
alongside you to help you build your
business where we where we join with you
where we where we go to battle with you
to create the kind of results that
you're looking
for what where would you be if you had a
community of
people that you could walk
alongside that you could say hey I'm
struggling with this here today I don't
know what to do in this aspect of my
business that's exactly what we put
together here in the client growth
accelerator program
and we work with you through every
single day you get immediate feedback
from from us and our community you get
access to our our courses and our
training I'm not here to pitch you on
this but I would encourage you that if
you're enjoying our content if you're
here go beyond that and start to work
with us to put everything together for
you and with you
okay because it's one thing to think
about taking action in a business it's
another thing to put your money where
your mouth is and actually start to take
action and one of the best ways to
actually virtually guarantee that things
are going to start working with you is
getting mentorship and joining a
community with people that are actually
doing it with a proven system with a
track record that is working right now
today to give you the Cutting Edge
updated information and that's the thing
is that what works today is different
than what worked a year ago six 6 months
ago
even and this irritates people it does I
get it because you want consistency
because you want predictable profits
because you don't want to be striving
and struggling and wishing that things
would pay you the kind of money that you
want to make you want to
know that you're going to be able to pay
your
bills this is why the launch model is
broken because the launch model has you
launching something and you have a
process that you you go out there and do
and then it ends up and it stops working
and you got to reinvent the wheel
constantly whereas the consistency that
we bring in when you do a subscription
with a membership and you build a
community the way that we teach our
clients and Mentor people on that
creates something where you might be
able to have a month where hey we're not
bringing in new sales but we have the
revenue from what we have put in and the
work that have done over time to be able
to sustain us okay and that becomes a
real business not just a fly by night
sales job if you want to Fly by Night
sales job you might as well go uh work
for somebody else selling solar or or
Roofing or or or cars if that's what you
want to do okay and that's and I don't
have anything to knock people that are
doing those types of things I actually
think that sometimes some of you need to
grow in your ability to sell to not be
afraid of other people and you might do
that through a direct sales company or
door-to-door sales or or traditional
sales as far as that goes if you need to
grow into doing that the way that I
actually learned sales was by working
for other people that were selling I
learned marketing and then the School of
Hard Knocks of going out there and
selling and getting rejected and
rejected and rejected again and again
and again and again some of y'all might
be like Jeremiah I don't want to get
rejected
I don't want it to not work out I want
consistency I I want a guarantee I want
something to
work I told you this in the beginning
there is no
guarantees it doesn't exist anybody
who's selling you that there is a
guarantee other than maybe a money back
guarantee on what they're they're
offering
you it's not real it's not rooted in
reality okay and so what we have to do
to be able to actually build a business
and listen I understand I'm probably
going to lose a bunch of people watching
this video because I just said that
because that's what they came to this
video to see is how to have a guaranteed
way that things work how to know for
certain that it's going to work can I
get you as as close as possible to that
that's what people hire me for and
that's what by the end of this video I
want to walk with you through and I want
to show you how to get as close as
possible to knowing that it's going to
work out to knowing that it's going to
come together to knowing that things are
going
to go from where you're at right
now to where you want to
be I have certainty every single morning
that when I might not have the results
that are coming in that I want and it
happens happens to me I'll launch a
campaign that I know or think or or
truly believe is going to work
out and then boom it falls flat
doesn't sell the way that I thought it
would doesn't produce the results that I
expected and you want to know what I got
to
do wipe my hands off shake my shoes out
and go after it again and get right back
up again and not say oh man I thought it
was going to work out I needed it to
work out this was my last
shot we tell ourselves these things
because our brain is focused on
survival and what ends up happening is
is that what we focus on and this is not
necessarily there's this whole like Law
of Attraction thing that's out there and
I and I do believe in in some of that
but can I tell you this there's actually
a neuroscience thing called the
reticular activating system in the brain
and the it's called the ra reticular
activating system and what it is is that
what whatever you focus on the brain
goes to work to find more
of and so if you're looking at
okay
what is not working right now what is
not coming together for me the way that
I need it to the way that I expect it to
the way that must happen for
me why is what I'm doing not marketable
why is nobody buying from me I lost
money running Facebook ads I don't know
if this is going to work your brain will
literally come up for validating reasons
why that's going to continue to
happen because that's all that it's
focused on it's focused on Survival
avoiding the thing instead you need to
learn how to
intentionally shift your focus towards
the thing that you are building the
thing that you are creating and have a
vision that is bigger than just what you
are experiencing or the past experiences
that didn't work out for
you and you might say well Jeremiah I
don't have certainty on this I need
certainty and then I will have that
that's why I'm here you told me you were
going to give me
certainty this is what we help people
with every single week in my coaching
program is to be able to point out
what's working what's not what is
consistent now how can you save yourself
time and effort and
energy of struggling when you do this
when you learn how to communicate
well and don't get offended by this I've
had a lot of people that're like excuse
me Mr Kowski who that H double hockey
sticks do you think you are telling me I
don't know how to communicate well
listen I would bet you might be a master
Communicator okay most of the coaches
mentors trainers and speakers that I
work with are they're really really good
at their message they're really really
good at connecting with people they've
been trained how to do this but what I'm
talking about is communicating your
value to people okay out there in the
marketplace and what I look for is that
when we are trying to Market a business
we're trying to see is it
marketable we have two stages with
people right here
cold and warm okay and so what I want to
do is I communicate differently with
people that I call a warm audience
versus a cold audience some of you right
now there's a mix of that watching this
video right here you might have seen a
suggestion or a recommendation on
YouTube to watch one of my videos and
this is your first time you're seeing a
video with me welcome subscribe continue
watching the videos we're going to be
putting out more video content let me
know as well in the comments what you
would like me to make videos on that's
called cold Market okay if I run a
Facebook ad or an Instagram ad or if I
put a Instagram real out there or a Tik
Tock video and somebody sees it because
the algorithm showed it to them that's
called a cold Market can I tell you this
the chances of you getting a sale from a
cold Market are very very slim and so
what your job job is this and this is
where most people I think get it wrong
is you're not just trying to sell to
people that are cold you're trying to
warm them up you're converting them from
cold to warm and then they become a hot
Prospect cold warm hot hot leads to
money they are at what's called a buying
temperature that is all the way up to
the top okay so your goal is whenever
you meet somebody that you don't know
right now you've never talked to them
strangers on the internet they are
cold okay and your job is to move them
to warm and then hot and then be able to
make money this is a skill set right
here based on your
communication ability when it comes to
sales and marketing and that's exactly
what we Mentor people on and that I want
to give you just a little bit of a crash
course on how that works here today okay
okay so whether you are putting out
content
on Instagram res whether you are doing
um let's let's let's say organic
Instagram reels we got Tik Tock
videos whether you have Facebook ads
okay whether you have YouTube
videos these are all different from each
other right they're not the
same but can I tell you
this and and what you what I put in a
Facebook ad might be different than what
I put in an Instagram reel or a Tik Tok
video or a YouTube video right this is a
long form YouTube training right here
whereas Tik Tok might be 60 seconds long
or a YouTube short or an Instagram real
might be under 2 minutes long a Facebook
ad I'm always looking to keep that the
main punch of it under 30 seconds and no
more than about 60 to 90 seconds for the
whole Facebook ad or Instagram ad or Tik
Tok ad but here's the thing and this is
where most people miss it this is
literally they make this mistake is that
these by themselves don't do anything
for you at
all and most people focus a lot of their
energy on this content creation
hamster wheel putting out content I ran
the Facebook ad I did the Instagram reel
no what you need to PE move people too
is from here these serve to attract and
draw the
attention of people but you want to move
them
towards what we call a
warming
exercise
exer exercise sometimes I forget how to
spell when I'm teaching that part of the
brain shuts down okay it's all right a
warming
exercise and they and by the way this
could literally be somebody who's
followed you for a year or
two but you're not going to necessarily
get them to buy from you off of a
YouTube video you're not generally and
and I tell people this all the time and
they don't like to hear it and it's just
I I if you follow me for a while you're
going to hear a lot stuff you don't want
to hear but it's the truth how many of
y'all can get an amen on that one right
I learned that one from my
[Laughter]
mama sending people from a Facebook ad
from an Instagram reel from a Tik Tok
video or a YouTube video to buy
something from you nine times out of 10
eight times out of 10 isn't going to
work it's going to fall flat and it's
going to be a waste of your time and
their time and you're going to be
struggling to get sales and this is
where a lot of people are like I tried
this before I tried to sell before and
and it just didn't work out for me
okay you have to move people to a
warming exercise now here's the cool
part about this these right
here for those of y'all that were
looking for the answer of how do I know
if it's marketable how do I know if it's
profitable these are actually baked
right into that process as well as the
warming
exercise these are actually how you
determine if what you're selling is
going to be marketable based on the
response and the reaction that you get
from people we call this direct response
marketing okay so you can look at the
data how many people watched the
Facebook ad click through and then took
some kind of an action and what is that
action that they might be taking they
either become a lead on your email list
maybe they upgrade to a low ticket
product s bucks
$17 of some kind and you might be saying
well Jeremiah I can't pay the bills on a
$17 or a low ticket or a free
product whatever you focus on you're
going to get more of if that's what
you're complaining about if that's what
your
excuses and listen you can get a as
angry at me as you want at that
statement
it's the truth you have to focus on the
fact that there is a process to this and
we live in a world today it's different
than it was two years ago it's different
than it was four years ago how many of
y'all wish things were how they were
before covid happened can I tell you
this things are not going back to the
way they were in fact they are are
evolving even faster and faster and I
was telling people this four years ago I
was telling them this 3 years ago I was
telling them this 2 years ago and they
ignored me and some of y'all might be
watching me right now you ignored what I
was saying and now you're watching this
you're like gosh he was spitting the
truth then he's spitting the truth now
or maybe you're questioning you're like
maybe things are going to get better if
a different president happens or maybe I
move somewhere or things like that
happen can I tell you that there's a
thing that's called
homeostasis where our mind and our body
r turns back to its comfort zone if we
are not
intentional to continue forward momentum
because of the survival instincts that
are built inside of our bodies our
brains to Keep Us
Alive and so maybe you might start a
program maybe you might join a coaching
program maybe you might start watching
some videos on YouTube and you start
getting excited and you start gaining
some CL Clarity and some understanding
as to what to happen and maybe you maybe
you got some clarity on what Niche to
take or or what offer to do can I show
you something real cool right now if
you're struggling to know what are some
niches to create a program with this is
where we I love to use AI to help us
brainstorm this just really really
quickly we can type in here what are 100
niches for a
membership based group coaching program
that I could Market with Instagram reels
Tik Tok videos YouTube or Facebook and
use the uh sales techniques of Sandy
Kowski that's my mom some of y'all might
not not know who Sandy Kowski is my mom
mentored people for years and I've
continued a lot of what her Legacy is as
well in this hello some of yall do know
who she is as well uh Dan Kennedy he
actually mentored myom he actually wrote
uh one of my favorite books right here
The Ultimate Sales letter by Dan Kennedy
I would highly highly recommend this
book right here if you're somebody
wondering how to do this Dan Kennedy and
Bill Glazer uh was a mentor to my mom as
well as and who owns a lot of Dan
Kennedy stuff Russell Brunson and by the
way I actually combine a lot of this now
is a method that I use for writing sales
copy is I use Sandy rowski Dan Kennedy
and Russell Brunson as like a sort of
Trinity
together of sales because their three
methods combined together the algorithm
and the AI starts to go to work to know
exactly what we're talking about okay so
there we go if we type that prompt in
right here this is going to give us an
answer right here creating a membership
based program you could do digital
marketing small business high-intensity
interval training yoga and meditation
parenting gluten-free living sustainable
gardening DIY renovation uh crypto
investment public speaking graphic
design training software development
cyber security fundamentals AI learning
virtual reality blogging for profit
podcasting look at all of these
different ideas luxury travel
planning budget hacks solo female travel
mindset and motivation grief counseling
and support film and
media magic and illusion techniques
artisan bread making cheese making at
home funu and space clearing pet
training the list goes on and on and on
and by the way almost all of these that
we see here we have people that we have
helped over the years create uh
memberships and stuff like that to
create to to create products and to sell
and to convert to paying members as far
as this goes so what you want to do is
you want to maybe find one or two of
these
okay let's say parenting young children
this is a really good one right here uh
generate me 50 sub niches or categories
that fit into the same framework as the
above four and then we're going to paste
that idea right here and this is one of
my number one ways of finding marketable
ideas for coaching or memberships or
programs that you could create literally
just two prompts with
AI what are 100 niches to be able to do
this and then you can pick one or two
that resonate with you and you can tell
it to to find what's called sub
niches it takes one of the categories
and then it Dives deeper to find another
category okay Early Child language
development sleep training for toddlers
positive
parenting these are all ideas that you
could use let's say parenting after
divorce let's dive even deeper into this
dive
even even deeper into parenting after
divorce and and find 50 sub
niches for this based on the framework
above
okay co-parenting dealing with legal
custody issues emotional
support maintaining Financial stability
so these could all become offers or
ideas that then could be marketable to
you you could literally take one of
these ideas if that's your Niche and
again might you might be saying well
that's not my Niche this doesn't matter
to me this is irrelevant to me go
through the
exercise go ask chat GPT these same
questions and see what it comes up for
you that can become your initial
Instagram reel Tik Tok video a YouTube
video you could make a YouTube video on
educating children through the nature of
relationships the role of therapy for
post divorce parenting all of these
different things as far as this goes
Facebook ads and then what you do is you
take people from one of those topics the
AI is a brainstorming assistant because
it'll trigger ideas for you of what your
strengths are what you're good at and
can I tell you this is that if you start
focusing on what am I really good at
what do people come to me for all the
time that they they say that I'm really
good at doing and you can even start
entering some of that stuff into the AI
we walk you through a lot of that in my
events and live trainings and coaching
that we do with people as soon as you
can kind of bring all of that together
you start to come up with an idea for an
offer that you can create to warm people
up to what you're doing now is it
guaranteed that this is going to make
you six figures off the bat no but can I
tell you this any of those ideas you can
make 10,000 20,000 $30,000 a month with
consistently you just have to learn the
skills to take people
from social
media and YouTube is social social media
as well advertising or organic content
and start to warm them up to the
possibility of working with you and so
how do you warm people up to the
possibility of working with you well you
learn how to sell and how to communicate
with people and it's not necessarily
just telling them what they're going to
get it's tapping into their emotional
buying triggers to increase
the
buying temperature that they have to
hotten it up so that they get more
excited you are stimulating their mind
their thoughts their feelings and their
emotions
consistently and that's what you need to
learn how to do is you create an
environment that is highly stimulating
specifically to the type of buyer that
you are looking for okay and so when you
can learn how to do this you end up
attracting people that you met over here
to wanting to work with you deeper
okay and this is an exercise a lot of us
may not know how to do or maybe we have
done this before I liken a lot of this
to dating or finding a spouse or finding
somebody that you might spend the rest
of your life with and I know a lot of
people by the way they're really good at
doing this in business but maybe they
struggle with it in their relationships
that's okay cuz you're a lot p pickier
in your relationships I'm a lot more
picky about who I want to be my spouse
than I am which I have an amazing wife
incredible mother to my children we got
a second one on the way you know but
when I when I met her I had
to be attractive I had to show up as the
person that she was looking for and my
goodness I did okay and that's exactly
what you need to learn how to do you
need to learn how to show up as the
person that your prospects are looking
for show up as the answer to all of
their prayers so that they can see
clearly that what they have been hoping
for and praying for and wishing would
show up in their life is now showing up
and you are that person okay so that's
where this initial stuff comes in that's
where the warming exercise draws them in
this is like the first date right here
by the way way though that's
it and far too many people I don't mean
to sound
uh gross here or
anything but they're trying to sleep
with their client getting them to make
by the way that's exactly what it is
that's the same energy that comes
across they're trying to sleep with
their client on the first date just
because they put a Facebook ad out there
just because they put a YouTube video
out there just because they did a
webinar
just because they launched an ebook and
then they get disappointed that people
are not buying from
them it's because there's so many other
people that are out there that are doing
this better that are really good at this
and again you can focus on I'm not good
at it I'm not I'm not this I'm not that
I don't have this I don't have that I
tried this I tried that and that's all
you're going to continue to get because
that's where you have your focus and so
you need to learn number one control
your
thoughts control your feelings control
emotions start looking at the bright
side of things start when you notice
that you got a negative thought coming
in on what you don't have access to
what's not working what's not going to
come together for you what you tried
before that didn't work I want you to
gently pinch yourself a little bit if
you if you can or or just and for me
it's now just a mental trigger oh I'm
going in that direction again put a stop
sign up mentally stop
sign and take a detour in your mind
towards the vision of where you're going
in your life anytime that negativity
starts to come up any time somebody says
something to you anytime you got a a a a
a friend that's trying to give you a
little bit of encouragement and then
they end up making you doubt
yourself
happens happens a lot
sometimes we got to change the voices
we're listening to sometimes we got to
change who we're scrolling and listening
to on social media and start listening
to more positive voices that start to
speak life into US of what the
possibilities are and the fact that you
are qualified right now to do the
incredible things that you want to go do
you might not have all the skills you
might not know all the things to do but
you are qualified right now to go after
it because can I tell you this you have
evidence in your life of being able to
find the answers that you don't know
what they are if you continue
looking and that's what I would
encourage you to do is continue watching
the videos that I put out here continue
engaging with my social media content
continue joining the live events that
we're doing you might see some of the
ads that we're running that are going to
come up on some of your social media
that's how we reach
people and then join the waiting list
for my client growth accelerator when we
open the doors to that I would love to
work with you to Mentor you to come
alongside you in our community on how to
do this and then how to take people from
just warming them up right because
warming people up is one part of the
process then how do you identify exactly
who you want to warm up cuz that's an
art there's an art to
that there's an art to identifying by
looking at the data and we use a
datadriven approach by looking at what
actions are people taking where are they
showing up we're not guessing anything
here this is 100% based on predictable
repeatable data but you might not have
the data initially that's where the AI
can help fill in some of the gaps saves
us ton of time tons of effort and
struggle and I'll tell you this all of
your competitors are using AI to do this
as well and so you need to learn to
start to use AI to your
advantage not to replace your voice I
don't believe that you should be using
AI to create your marketing
anymore or not even most of your content
anymore but use it to brainstorm ideas
that then trigger your own mind to
become creative and when we can get out
of fight ORF flight when we can get out
of the struggle constantly trying to you
know borrow from people to pay Paul and
I'm and I'm not able to pay my bills and
we can get out of the scarcity mindset
and we can start to focus on okay even
though I might not be able to pay my
rent this
month I can focus on where I'm going
because I know and I'm trusting the
process and I'm trusting that I am on a
path that's going to take me from step
one to step two to step three to step
four and that's exactly what I love to
do with people is we have a system now
that we've developed inside of my
coaching program to take you from step
one to step two to step three to step
forward to where you don't have to
wonder what are the things that I need
to do next
okay and so in that again jump on the
waiting list continue engaging with my
videos and let me know below what aspect
of what I just talked about today would
you like me to focus on
next I know one of the videos we're
going to be creating is about sales and
stuff like that what would you like to
know about sales what would you like to
know about this process right here what
about what would you like to know about
what comes after this process right here
that's a whole other
training okay that's a whole other
topic about once you get people from
here to hear and you warm them up then
how do you close the sale and I'd love
to work with you through that and I'd
love to walk with you through that here
on my Channel all right so let me know
below what other topics you'd love us to
talk about what kind of content you'd
love us to create and thanks for
watching thanks for staying tuned into
what we're sharing and what we're what
we're um teaching people on the internet
here today my name is Jeremiah Kowski
and again I'd love to see you in our
coaching program in the group
accelerator the coaching accelerator
program my client growth accelerator
program we'll talk soon everybody have a
good one